黄日鏘 Wong Yat Cheong Jacky

Programmer Website:

Email: jackywongboy84@gmail.com

Address: Kowloon, Hong Kong

https://wongyat88.github.io/

Working Experience

Programmer

Gold Label Technology Limited, 2022/3 ~ Present

- Led the full lifecycle development of 5+ web-based applications for inventory, fixed assets, and POS systems.
- Develop diverse web-projects using technologies like Vite Vue3 (CSR), Nuxt3 (SSR), React (CSR), Next.JS (SSR/SSG), Django (SSR), Django REST Framework, Express.js, Nitro & Spring Boot.
- Developed 2 AI related projects, Human Movement Detection (computer vision and RFID) and AI Chatbot with RAG (AWS Bedrock).
- Developed 5+ Android and desktop applications using Java, integrating RFID technology for advanced inventory management solutions.
- Experience on cloud server setups on Linux and Windows Server 2019, configuring web servers (IIS, Nginx), securing connections with SSL/SSH, and automating database backups.

Technician Support Service

Speedy Group Corporation Limited, 2021/7 ~ 2022/2

- Performed hardware maintenance and troubleshooting for PC systems,
 enhancing operational efficiency.
- Configured and managed Windows domain environments and network access points, ensuring robust network connectivity.
- Designed and developed a web-based Substitute System for managing school teacher assignments.
- Utilized Python and OpenCV for developing an automated system to detect QR code data and rename files.

Skills

Programming Languages

Python, Java, JavaScript, TypeScript, HTML5, CSS, PHP

Frameworks and Tools

Django REST, Flask, Express, Vue3, Nuxt 3, React, Next.js, Spring Boot, Android

Libraries

Tailwind CSS, Bootstrap5, JWT, Prisma, Axios, OpenCV, NumPy, Pandas

Databases

MariaDB, MySQL, SQLite, MongoDB

AI/ML Technologies

PyTorch, YOLO, RAG

Systems and Servers

Windows Server, Linux (Ubuntu), Nginx, Apache, SSL, SSH

Summary

With over 5 years of programming experience, I am proficient in system design for front-end, back-end, mobile, and desktop applications. I can create REST APIs, web sockets with authorization, and custom middleware. I am eager to learn new coding languages and explore new technologies, always aiming to enhance the user experience from the customer's perspective.

Education

MSc Computer Science
University of Hong Kong, HKSAR
September 2023 – Present

BSc Information Technology of Business Coventry University, United Kingdom September 2017 - August 2020

Certifications

Common Recruitment Examination (CRE) HKSAR, November 2020

Language

- Cantonese (Native)
- English (Fluent)
- Mandarin (Fluent)

Other Skills

- GitHub Copilot
- Stable Diffusion & LoRa
- GPT-SoVITS
- Putty
- AWS Bedrock
- GitHub / Git Control